-Hi.
-Hi! Hi, Ben.
- 안녕
- 안녕, 밴
-Hi.
-We have a bathroom emergency.
- 안녕
- 화장실 급한데...
Go ahead.
빨리 가
Before we do, are any of Joey's
special "romance" magazines in there?
가기 전에...
거기 이상한 잡지 있어?
-No.
-Okay, all clear.
- 아니
- 그럼 됐다
Thanks, Phoebe.
고마워요, 피비
That's Rachel.
난 레이첼인데...
But whatever.
어쨌거나
Could you do me a big favor?
진짜 부탁 하나만 들어줘
I have a meeting
at the dean's office.
나 중요한 회의가 있거든
Can you watch Ben for an hour?
밴을 1시간만
봐 줄 수 있어?
-What about Monica?
-She isn't home.
- 모니카는?
- 집에 없어
So it would just be me alone?
나 혼자서 해야 돼?
Ben would be there.
밴도 있잖아
What's the matter?
문제 있어?
I've never done that before.
Me and him, alone.
그런 거 해본 적이 없어
그런 애랑 단 둘이
He's not an ex-con.
전과자도 아닌데...
Okay, okay...
그래, 알았어
-What do I do with him?
-I don't know, talk to him.
- 뭐 하고 놀아야 되지?
- 몰라, 얘길 하든지
Entertain him. Keep him alive.
재미있게 해 줘
살려만 둬
-Okay.
-Ben, come here.
- 알았어
- 밴, 이리와 봐
I'm gonna leave you here with
Aunt Rachel for about an hour, okay?
레이첼 아줌마랑 한 시간만
같이 놀아, 알았지?
Gonna be okay?
괜찮지?
-I think so.
-I wasn't talking to you.
- 그럼
- 너한테 말한 거 아냐
The One With The Truth About London
What about the second minister?
I kind of liked him.
두 번째 본 목사님은 어때?
난 괜찮은데
-You mean the spitter?
-Come on. He wasn't that bad.
- 그 아무데나 침 뱉던 인간?
- 아냐, 그렇게 나쁘진 않은데
Easy for you to say,
you'd be wearing a veil.
말 하기야 쉽지
얼굴 가리고 다녀야 될 걸
-And the third guy?
-He kept staring at your chest.
- 세 번째 후보는?
- 니 가슴만 쳐다보더라
Can you blame him?
내가 예쁜걸 어떡해?
I don't like the idea of
me saying, "I do"...
나만 예쁘다고 하면 되지
while he's thinking,
"I'd do it too."
그 사람도
그렇게 생각하는 건 싫어
-Well, then we still have a problem.
-With what?
- 그래도 여전히 문제네
- 뭐가?
We need someone to perform our wedding
but they're all boring or annoying...
보통 주례들은
지루하고 재미없잖아
or keep staring at the ladies.
아님 여자들만 쳐다 보든가
You should have one of us do it.
우리 중에 하나가 하지 뭐
We're getting "married" married,
not "6th-grade" married.
우리 소꿉장난 하는 거 아냐
No, it's a real thing.
진짜로 하는거라구
Anyone can be ordained on the lnternet
and perform weddings and stuff.
인터넷으로 자격을 얻어서
해주는 사람 있던데
여기요!
I call it!
뭐야? 내가 말했는데!
What? It was my idea!
고맙지만
니들한테 부탁 안 한다
Thank you very much, but neither
of you is marrying us.
친구의 호의를
그렇게 무시해?
Does calling it not mean
anything anymore?
제대로 된 주례 선생님을
모셔오는 거라구
We're having a legitimate
clergy member.
제대로라는 말은,
동성연애자면서
And when I say legitimate,
I mean gay...
침 아무한테나
안 뱉는 사람
and in control of his saliva.
Ben, you know, when you were a baby...
밴, 너 애기 때
we'd hang out all the time.
항상 같이 놀았어
I was your daddy's girlfriend.
아빠 여친 이었거든
But you're not anymore.
근데요
지금은 아니잖아요
-No, I'm not.
-Because you guys were on a break..
- 그래, 아냐
- 깨졌잖아요...
Hey, we were not on a..
야, 그런게 아니라...
-When's my daddy coming back?
-Fifty-two minutes.
- 아빠 언제 와요?
- 52분 남았어
So no brothers or sisters, huh?
형제는 없어?
You know, I had two sisters
and we just tortured each other.
난 세자매 였는데
매일 으르렁 거리면서 살았지
- 진짜요? 어떻게요?
- 아니, 그게, 그러니까
-Really? Like how?
-Well, you know, we would...
we'd repeat everything
the other said...
말하는 거 흉내 내고
or we'd jump out of closets
to scare each other...
옷장 속에 숨어있다가
깜짝깜짝 놀래 키고
or switch the sugar with salt
so they put salt on their cereal.
설탕 통에 소금 넣어서
소금 넣은 시리얼 먹게 하고
That's a good one.
재밌었겠다
-Yeah, you like that one?
-Yeah, you're funny.
- 그치, 재밌지?
- 네, 웃기네요
I'm funny?
내가 웃겨?
Oh, thank God.
휴, 다행이네
Well, hey, I got a ton of these.
밴, 얘기 꺼리 더 많은데
You take a quarter...
동전을 하나 가지고
and you blacken the edge, right?
가장자리를 까맣게 칠해, 응?
And then you say,
"I bet you can't roll this quarter...
그러고서 '너 이거 얼굴에서
안 떨러지게 해서'
to your chin without it
leaving your face."
'턱까지 못 굴릴 껄?'
하는거야
And when they do it, they're left with
a line down the center of their face.
애들이 그걸 해낸 뒤
얼굴이 어떻게 될지 상상해봐
Can I do it to you?
아줌마 한테 해봐도 돼요?
I'm funny, Ben, but I'm not stupid.
밴, 난 재밌긴 해도
멍청인 아냐
So did you find anyone
to marry you yet?
주례 찾았어?
No, but "Horny for Monica" minister
called...
아니, 근데 모니카 가슴 쳐다 본
사람이 전화 했더라구
우리가 아직 사귀는지 묻더군
wondering if we're still together.
- 아마 못 찾을 것 같애
- 그럼 내가 해줄께
-We'll never find anybody.
-Then let me do it.
- 조이...
- 생각해 봤는데
-Joey..
-I've been thinking.
명색이 배운데, 사람들
앞에서 떨진 않겠지
I'm an actor, so I won't
get nervous in front of people.
침도 안 뱉고
모니카 가슴도 안 쳐다 볼께
I won't spit and I won't stare
at Monica's breasts.
엉덩이라면 모를까
Everyone knows I'm an ass man.
- 맞다
- 중요한건
-That's true.
-The most important thing...
니들을 모르는 사람이
아니잖아
is, it won't be some stranger
who barely knows you.
It'll be me. And I swear,
I'll do a really good job.
나라구
나 잘할 수 있어, 맹세해
Plus, I love you guys and it
would really mean a lot to me.
내가 니들을 좋아하고
내게도 의미가 있잖냐?
괜찮겠다
Might be kind of cool.
- 그럼, 내가 하는거지?
- 그래, 해 봐라
-So I can do it?
-Yeah, you can do it.
진짜지! 좋아!
All right! Okay!
주례사 준비해야겠다
Okay, I gotta get started
on my speech.
잠깐
Wait a minute.
인터넷 성직자도
계속 섹스 할 수 있지?
Internet ministers
can have sex, right?
Coming.
가요
I have a bone to pick with you.
너한테 할 말있어
-Uh-oh.
-Yes.
- 어머나
- 그래
Ben learned a little trick.
밴이 어디서
이상한걸 배웠거든
-Oh, did he pull the old..?
-That's right, that's right.
- 아, 그 옛날꺼...?
- 응, 그거
Saran wrap on the toilet seat...
세란이 변기를
비닐로 싸서
so the pee goes everywhere.
오줌이 사방팔방으로
다 튀던거
-Oh, that.
-Yeah, that.
- 아, 그거
- 그래, 그거
You know I hate practical jokes.
그런 지나친 장난
싫어하는거 알지
They're mean, they're stupid and
I don't want my son learning them.
너무 짓궂고, 멍청해 보이고
내 아들은 몰랐으면 해
Saran wrap on the toilet seat?
Isn't that just a little funny?
변기를 비닐로 싼 얘기?
그냥 웃으라고 한건데?
-I was barefoot.
-Oh.
- 내가 맨발이었거든
- 어머
Tell me, the toilet thing is the
only thing you taught him, right?
그 변기 얘기밖에 안 했지?
Yes.
응
-Hey.
-Say hello to Reverend Joey Tribbiani.
조이 트리비아니 주례님께
인사들 하셔
-You got ordained?
-Yeah.
- 자격증이야?
- 그럼
Just got off the lnternet.
Man, there's a lot of porn out there.
인터넷에서 방금 받았지
근데 야한 사이트 많던데
Our minister.
주례 선생님
I started on what I'm gonna say
for the ceremony. Want to hear it?
식장에서 할 말 준비했는데
들어 볼래?
Listen, this is just
the first draft, so...
들어봐, 초고이긴 하지만
"We are gathered here today
on this joyous occasion...
'우린 모니카와 챈들러의
특별한 사랑을'
to celebrate the special love
that Monica and Chandler share.
'축하해 주기 위해
여기 한 자리에 모였습니다'
It is a love based on
giving and receiving...
'서로 주고 받고 가진 것을
나누는 것을'
as well as having and sharing.
'바탕으로 한 사랑입니다'
And the love that they give
and have is shared and received.
'가진 것을 서로 주는 것은
나눔을 받는 것이고'
And through this having and giving...
'가진 것과 주는 것을 통하여'
and sharing and receiving...
'나눔과 받음이 되고'
'우리도 역시
나눔과 사랑과 가짐'
we too can share and love
and have...
'그리고 받음'
and receive."
그 침 뱉던 사람한테
전화할까?
Should we call the spitter?
- 안녕, 레이첼
- 안녕
-Hey, Rachel.
-Hi.
놀랍네
여긴 왠 일이야?
What a surprise.
What are you doing here?
이 근처에 왔다가
I was just in the neighborhood...
너희 집 지나는 길에
'캐롤하고'
and I passed by your building and
thought, "What's up with Carol...
'귀염둥이 밴은 뭐하나?' 해서
and sweet little Ben?"
- 반갑다, 들어와
- 응
-That's nice. Well, come on in.
-Okay.
커피 마시면서 얘기하자
I'll make some coffee
and we can chat.
좋지, 딱 이야
I'd love that.
I would love that.
우리 귀염둥이 밴은?
So where is sweet little Ben?
귀여운 꼬마보고 싶은...
I would love to have a little..
찾았다!
I found him!
재밌지, 응
이리와
Very funny. Come here.
바로 그것 때문에 내가
여기 온거야, 알겠니?
That is exactly why I've
come here to talk to you, okay?
- 레이첼, 설탕 넣을까?
- 응, 근데...
-Rachel, you want sugar?
-Yes, but..
설탕통에 소금 넣었니?
Do I want sugar in my coffee?
아니, 그냥 우유나 좀 넣어줘
고마워
No, just some milk would
be good, Carol. Thanks.
내가 어제 말 한 것들 생각나?
Remember all that stuff
I taught you yesterday?
'내가 어제 말 한 것들 생각나?'
"Remember all that stuff
I taught you yesterday?"
- 따라 하지마
- '따라 하지마'
-Don't do that.
-"Don't do that."
- 너희 아빠는 그런 장난 싫어해
- '너희 아빠는 그런 장난 싫어해'
-Your dad doesn't like pranks.
-"Your dad doesn't like pranks."
- 이런, 젠장!
- '이런, 젠장!'
-Oh, damn it.
-"Oh, damn it!"
그런 말 하지마
No! Don't say that.
- 이런, 젠장!
- 따라 하지마
-Damn it!
-Go back to repeating.
- 끓는다!
- 으, 끓어!
-Damn it!
-Oh, crap.
'으, 끓어!'
"Oh, crap!"
좋아
조금 더 적었거든, 들어봐
Okay, I got some more written, ready?
Yeah, okay.
응, 해봐
"When I think of the love that these
two givers and receivers share...
'제가 이 두 명의 진실한
사랑 나눔이를 생각하면'
I can't help but envy the lifetime
ahead of having and loving...
'평생 동안의 사랑 나눔이
부러울 따름입니다'
and giving.." And then I can't
think of a good word for right here.
'주는 것...'
여기서 좋은 말이 생각이 안나
-How about "receiving"?
-Yes!
- '받음' 어때?
- 그거야!
See, Joe, not that that's not great...
조이, 멋지지 않다는 건
아닌데
but one cool thing about having
a friend perform the ceremony...
친구가 결혼식을
주관 하는게 좋은 이유는
is that it can be about us.
모든 게 우리에 관한 것이다
이거지
It can be more personal.
You can tell stories about us.
더 친근하게
우리 얘기를 하면 되잖아
좋아! 런던에서 사귀게 된
얘기나 해야겠다
Okay! Maybe I'll talk about London,
when you hooked up.
단지 사귀게 됐다는게 아니라
Only I won't say "hooked up"...
'아름다운 둘 만의 여행의
시작이라고 말하지'
I'll say, "began their
beautiful journey...
-There you go.
-by doing it."
- 바로 그거야
- '같이 자서'
-Joe.
-Okay, all right.
- 조이
- 그래, 알았어
So how did it happen?
Did your eyes meet across the room...
그럼 어떻게 된거야?
갑자기 불꽃이 팍팍 튀었나
then you're in the bathtub
and she's feeding you strawberries?
넌 욕조 안에 있었고
모니카가 딸기 먹여주고?
-Isn't that what happened to you?
-Yeah!
- 네 얘기 하는거지?
- 맞아!
I call that "London style."
그런걸 '런던 스타일'
이라고 하지
That didn't happen with us.
우린 그러진 않았어
Maybe you should say it is,
because "London style" sounds nice.
그냥 그렇게 얘기하자
'런던 스타일' 멋있는데
Okay, uh...
좋아, 음
I was sad that night because
this guy thought I was Ross' mom.
그때 만나던 사람이 내가 로스
엄마라고 생각해서 너무 슬펐거든
And Chandler was really sweet
and he consoled me and...
챈들러가 너무 친절하게
날 위로해 줬고
-we drank too much.
-Yeah, baby.
- 술도 많이 마셨어
- 그래, 슬슬 나온다
I was a gentleman and I walked her to
her hotel room and said good night.
신사답게 호텔 방까지
데려다 주고 '잘자'라고 했지
Oh.
-But then, later that night..
-Yeah, baby.
- 근데, 그날 늦게...
- 그래, 그거야
Cute P.J.s. Really living it up
here in London, huh?
예쁜 잠옷이라
런던에 산다는게 진짠가 보네?
Well, I wasn't exactly
expecting company after...
음, 이 늦은 시간에
누가 오리라곤...
9:15.
9시 15분 밖에 안됐네
Is Joey here?
조이 있어?
Last I saw he was with a bridesmaid
and a bucket of strawberries.
아까 딸기 바구니 들고
신부 친구랑 있던데
You're not still upset about
what that guy told you, are you?
그 남자가 말한 거 때문에
아직 화난 건 아니지?
Wouldn't you be?
너 같으면?
It's been a really emotional time
and you've had a lot to drink...
너무 감정적이 된 거 같아
술도 많이 마시고 해서...
You have to let that go, okay?
잊어 버려, 알았지?
You were the most beautiful
woman in the room tonight.
오늘밤 여기서
니가 제일 아름다워
Really?
정말?
장난 같아? 진짜
너 오늘 예뻐 보인다
You kidding? You're the most
beautiful woman in most rooms..
우와, 왜 그래?
Whoa, what's going on?
즉흥적인 거지?
We just made out.
- 우리 하는 거야?
- 아니, 여기까지
-We're making out?
-Not anymore.
- 이러지 말자
- 알아, 그냥 재미로
-But we don't do that.
-I know, I thought it would be fun.
얼마나 마셨어?
How drunk are you?
이걸 원할 정도로
니가 죄책감 안 들게 할 정도로
Enough to know I want to do this. Not
so much that you should feel guilty.
적당하군
That's the perfect amount.
- 이상한게 뭔지 알아?
- 뭔데?
-You know what's weird?
-What?
- 어색하지 않다는거
- 맞아
-This doesn't feel weird.
-I know.
- 키스 정말 잘하네
- 네 명 이상 해 봤거든
-You're a really good kisser.
-Well, I have kissed over four women.
침대 속으로 갈까?
Want to get under the covers?
Okay.
와, 진짜 빠르네!
Wow, you are really fast!
빠르면 좋아할 줄 알았지
It bodes well for me
that speed impresses you.
- 벗은 걸 같이 보자
- 그래
-We're gonna see each other naked.
-Yep.
- 동시에?
- 셋 셀까?
-At the same time?
-Count of three?
하나, 둘, 셋
One, two, three.
그럼, 우리의 우정이
끝났다고 할 수 있겠군
Well, I think it's safe to say
our friendship is effectively ruined.
우리 사이엔 우정이 없었지
Eh, we weren't that close anyway.
조이, 조이, 조이!
Joey, Joey, Joey!
안녕
Hey.
안녕, 조이
영화보고 있었는데
Hey, Joe.
I was just watching a movie...
오, 미안해, 친구야
Oh, dude, I'm so sorry.
아니야, 아니야!
No!
괜찮아, 나 아직
그녀랑 같이있어
It's cool, I'm still
with my bridesmaid.
콘돔 어딨어?
Where are the condoms?
내 가방 안에
In my bag over there.
한 개만 남겨 둘래?
Could you leave me one?
For just you?
너 혼자...?
응
Yeah.
알았어
여깄다, 친구
All right. There you go, buddy.
즐겨라
Go nuts.
That's what that was?
그거야?
If I hadn't left you one, you two
might've never gotten together.
너에게 남겨두지 않았으면
너희들은 함께 하지 못했을걸
Imagine if I had sent that hooker
like I was gonna?
그 창녀를 방에
보냈다고 생각해봐
It's like it was in the stars.
황홀해
Yeah, totally meant to be.
그래, 정말 그렇지
Tell him who you originally
wanted to hook up with that night.
정말 함께 하고 싶었던
사람이 누군지 얘기해봐
-What?
- 뭐?
What?
뭐라구?
Who did you originally
want to hook up with?
누구랑 함께 하고 싶었어?
Okay, fine, but please don't be upset.
알았어, 좋아
근데 화내지는 마
I was really depressed, okay?
And really drunk.
정말 기분 꿀꿀 했어, 알아?
술도 많이 마셨고
I wanted something stupid and
meaningless. I just wanted sex.
의미 없는 바보 같은 짓을
하고 싶었어, 섹스
So, when I went to your
room that night...
니방에 갔을때
I was actually looking for Joey.
사실 조이를 찾고 있었어
Yeah, baby.
잘했어, 자기
No, baby.
안 돼, 자기
Oh, my God.
맙소사
You came looking for Joey?
조이 찾으러 왔었다구?
-Were you planning on telling me this?
-No, I didn't think it was important.
- 얘기하려고 했니?
- 아니, 중요치 않다고 생각했어
It's not important?
중요하지 않아?
중요하지 않다고?
If it wasn't for a bridesmaid,
you'd be marrying him.
들러리만 아니었으면
조이랑 결혼하겠네
Do you know how unbelievably
glad I am that Joey wasn't there?
근데 조이가 없었다는게
얼마나 다행인줄 알아?
Hey!
뭐야!
나도 남잔데
아직도 감정이 남았어
I'm a man of the cloth
but I still have feelings.
너 주례 할 꿈도 꾸지마,
알았어?
There's no way you're
doing this wedding now, okay?
뭐라구? 불공평해
내잘못이 아니잖아
What? That's not fair.
It's not my fault.
들러리랑 있었던거고
I was with my bridesmaid.
내가 모니카 한테
그런다고 했겠냐?
And who's to say
I would've said yes?
내말은, 그랬을꺼야
I mean, I would've said yes.
니가 문제를 크게 만드는 거야
You are making way too
big a deal out of this.
다 잘됐잖아
Everything worked out okay.
기분 나쁘다고
알았어?
It's just weird, okay?
결혼서약 하면서 너랑 모니카를
떠올리고 싶지 않다구
I don't want to be saying my vows with
the mental image of you and Monica.
뭐가 뭔지 모르겠다
좀 걸어야겠다
I need.. I don't know what I need.
I need a walk.
- 잠깐, 큰 문제 아니잖아
- 나한테는 큰 문제야
-Wait, Chandler, it's not a big deal.
-It is to me.
배트맨이랑 자놓고
로빈이랑 살길 원하는 거잖아
You wanted to sleep with Batman
and settled for Robin.
- 미치겠군
- 안 돼, 로빈은 게이야
-This is crazy.
-No, Robin is so gay.
-So now what have we agreed?
-No more pranks.
- 우리가 뭐에 동의했지?
- 더 이상 장난치지 않는거
-What else?
-You and Daddy were not on a break.
- 또?
- 아줌마랑 아빠가 깨진게 아니라는거
Very good.
좋아
Rachel, what are you doing here?
레이첼, 여기서 뭐해?
I'm just visiting
my good friend Carol.
친한 친구, 캐롤 보러 왔어
-Your good friend?
-Yeah.
- 친한 친구?
- 응
What's her last name?
성이 뭔데?
Carol...
캐롤
-Lesbian.
-Nice.
- 레즈비언
- 멋지군
By the way, that line down my face...
근데, 얼굴에 있던 줄...
The line that prompted a student
in my last class of the day to say:
그 줄말야
마지막 수업의
한 학생이 그러던데
'선생님, 세수 하셨어요?'
"Dude, don't you ever wash your face?"
알았어, 미안
말 안해서 미안해
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
내 아들한테 그런거
더는 가르치지 말아줘
I don't want you teaching my son
that stuff anymore.
- 알았어?
- 좋아, 알았어
-Okay?
-Fine. Fine.
그런거 가르쳐주면 날 재밌는
아줌마라고 불렀는데
Once I taught him that stuff,
he called me "fun Aunt Rachel."
재밌는 아줌마 되는거 좋았어
And I loved being fun Aunt Rachel.
I'm glad you guys were bonding but..
계속 만나는건 좋은데...
Look, he doesn't have any siblings.
근데, 걔는 형제가 없잖아
Somebody has to teach him this stuff.
누군가 이런걸
가르쳐 줘야 하는데말야
I haven't taught him anything
a normal 6-year-old doesn't know.
어쨌든 나이에 안 맞는건
안 가르쳤어
-Crap!
-I gotta go.
- 끊는다!
- 가야겠어
-Hey.
- 뭐해?
- 왔냐?
You want this scone? It came for me
but it would rather sleep with you.
이거 먹을래? 내가 시킨건데
너 하고 잠들고 싶데
아무일 없었잖아
Nothing even happened.
I just don't want you to be upset.
그냥 니가 화내는게 싫어
어떻게 화를 안내?
How can I not be upset?
멋진 여성과
사랑에 빠졌지만
I finally fall in love
with this fantastic woman...
널 처음 원했다는걸 알았는데
and it turns out
she wanted you first.
그래, 근데 잠깐 이었잖아
Yeah, for like a half an hour
one night.
챈들러, 근데 널
평생 원하잖아
Chandler, she wants you
for the rest of her life.
너희가 함께 하는걸 볼거고
We look at you and we
see you together, and it just...
it fits, you know?
딱이야, 알아?
And you just know
it's gonna last forever.
영원할거야
그게 해야될 말이다
That's what you should say.
뭐가?
What?
결혼식때
해야할 말이라고
When you're marrying us,
that's what you should say.
정말? 그렇게 말할까?
Really? I could do it?
너무 좋다
I'd love you to do it.
친구
Hey.
그렇게 얘기해
꼭 그렇게
But those are the words.
Those exact words.
근데 정확히
기억은 못하겠고
Well, I don't remember exactly but...
주는 것 받는 것 소유하는 것
나누는 것이란 말이 많았던거 같은데
it's pretty much about having
and giving and sharing and receiving.
-So you guys doing okay?
-Yeah.
- 괜찮아?
- 응
We talked and Monica made me
see that I overreacted a little bit.
모니카가 내가 약간
오버했다고 하더군
-Some things are more important.
-Yeah, baby.
- 더 중요한 일들이 있는데
- 그래
I'm really glad you guys are okay,
but I just keep thinking...
너희들이 괜찮다니 기쁘네
근데 계속 궁금한게
what would've happened
if you two had hooked up.
너희 둘이 연결 됐으면
어떻게 됐을까?
Honey, dinner's ready!
자기야, 저녁 됐어!
What's my little chef
got for me tonight?
오늘은 뭘 준비하셨나요
귀여운 요리사님?
-Your favorite.
-Ho, ho, ho...
자기가 좋아하는 걸로요
fried stuff with cheese.
후라이랑 치즈군
And lots of it!
그것도 많이!
Thanks, sweetheart.
고마워, 우리 예쁜이
Give me a little sugar...
이리와 봐...
Here we go, here we go, here we go.
자 자 자
How you doing?
안녕, 음식들?
-Hey.
-Hey!
또 맡기게 돼서 미안한데
I'm sorry to do this again, but
could you look after Ben for a bit?
밴 좀 잠시 봐줄래?
학교회의가 있어서
I've got this meeting at school...
쟤가 '재밌는' 아줌마를 찾네
and he asked for his
fun Aunt Rachel.
Well, of course I will watch him.
그럼, 그렇게 할께
재밌게 보냈지, 밴?
We have fun, don't we, Ben?
- 알았어, 있다보자, 친구
- 그래
-See you later, pal.
-Okay.
'바보'
Wait a minute. Ben, I can't do it.
- 잠깐만 밴, 난 이거 못해
- 뭐?
- 등에 뭐 있어
-You got something on your back.
-What?
That's great. That is great.
멋지네, 멋져
What did we just finish
talking about, Ben?
방금 무슨얘기 했었지?
'방금 무슨 얘기 했었지?'
"What did we just finish
talking about, Ben?"
좋아, 이리와
너 이제 큰일 났어!
That's it! Come here!
-You're in big trouble, young man!
-No, wait.
밴, 이리와!
장난 아니야!
Ben, come here! I am not kidding!
그러지마
You guys, hold it. Seriously..
맙소사!
Oh, my God!